foreign
[Music]
I welcome all of you today to discuss
this stock that is ICICI Lombardo
General Insurance
hello everyone I also welcome you all
so today let us discuss
the stock step by step
to let us go with our process tip
so let us check the stock trend
so this is a stock I opened now here and
uh
for the stock trend
I will make it
this one we'll check with EMA
[Music]
I'll put 20 and 40
. generally we check exponential moving
average whether that is 15 then the
stock is great
whether it is nearer to 50 then the
stock is good
so yeah correct you're right and as we
see here
the moving average
it is just touching so it is just go
down
[Music]
so neither it is in a obtained nor
attendant downtrend
because it is also getting Consolidated
here so this Market is in the sideway
so presently it is a sideway
[Music]
yeah
and now let us
check
what is a
[Music]
let us go to the pattern
so on Day candle Day candle if I check
this
so you know we always cross check
the chart pattern
with this
chart pattern list
so here if you see closely
on a short term
the flag pattern is showing there
yeah correct
so here it is
no
a short term
it is showing as a flag
so definitely
[Music]
we need to wait till it break out
then it'll move
so in a short term it looks like here
so even if you see this
[Music]
okay approximately it may go here
one three five two even with flat
pattern
but somehow it also giving one more
[Music]
that is w
yeah all right
so yeah this is also giving
you see this
[Music]
making W pattern also so in any way I
think it will
go 40
one three double nine thousand four
hundred
that we need to check but in the short
term
it may reach Tilly
[Music]
yeah thousand uh 294
basically you know we are
analyzing this for a long term
but you know that we just studied on a
short term also
if you see there is a big
[Music]
w
even this is also visible
[Music]
but it will take a lot of time that's
why you know for long term we are
discussing here
even if you take on the weekly time
frame
[Music]
here also it is making W pattern
yeah yeah correct
[Music]
so
let's see what is going to happen
we see on the monthly or so it is yes
showing me
the W pattern
[Music]
so these are the pattern presently it is
showing
[Music]
next is the volume
let me check the bundle
[Music]
presently the volume is used Nest nearer
to that tortilla
[Music]
that means some buying and selling is
going on
so
if you want to confirm that EMA so we
can check even
the delivery percentage
so that is even if you go to any website
[Music]
so
we select here
from last
one month what is happening
you see it's a very good volume delivery
percentage you know 75 percent 45
75 65
there is some good accumulation is going
on here
normally we say about 20 20 to 30
percent it is good but here it is better
[Music]
anyway so now let us check
relative strength
relative strengths
will make this button known
to relative strength normally we say
about 40
it's good
the relative strength is touching the
16th
that relative strength is touching 60
now
and yeah it is in a
bit strong Zone
let us check what is that or
support and resistance
so we see this support now let us draw
it to now
the board let us take one horizontal
line
[Music]
let us make it thick
in little bit red color
[Music]
if you see this already it is it has
taken
hmm
how many times see
one two three four five six seven more
times it has taken up support at this
level so it's a strong support Zone
[Music]
and also we know that covet is again
arriving
so maybe that's why it's becoming a
chart it's becoming strong so there are
chances that
you know that it will grow
[Music]
anyway this is One support and
this is one more support
to support we need is important because
even if it's the stock is falling
will come to know at what level it will
fall
[Music]
foreign
this resistance
to resistance is presently here because
already in the past it has taken this
resistance you see
[Music]
so the next resistance
will be at
[Music]
nearly
1300. nearly
once if it crosses yes it will move
1350 something like that
anyway so
this will happen I could see there is a
strong
chat pattern
[Music]
so what is the next step
fundamentals
so let us check the fundamentals
now
for the fundamentals let us check here
even analysis
they suggested 71 percent
this is
[Music]
a good
and we can
look for for the study and investment
this is what it says
and when we come to the holding
[Music]
so let us check the holding
here to see the foreign institutions
they are reduced there
[Music]
stake
whereas
domestic
investors they have increased
mistake
so that means uh even a domestic
investors believe that this is going to
give a
good returns
also when we see financially
or even if we compare or if we compare
with others
[Music]
the company has reduced the debts it's
very important the company is almost
there to Freedom
company has been maintaining the healthy
dividends of 24.3 percent
these are the plus points promoters only
have reduced this holding patterning
that should not be much matter
so compared to views like you know SBI
life hdf is live
here what we see normally is
dead to equity ratio is zero that means
debt free company it is
zero debts
it's showing our return on Capital
employee it's showing 142 percent
[Music]
yeah these are the good one
now let us
check the
profit and loss
so
net profit is also on the
plus side
so in the fundamentals yeah this much we
can see
[Music]
let us see the put call ratio so what it
says
even the put call ratio presently it
says that
no the maximum page is 1200 and yes here
also it says it is it will go up till
thousand three hundred
even January also it may stay till 1300.
[Music]
so let us put the hip retracement
and check
[Music]
what will be the support and resistance
little bit in a more precise way
[Music]
so let us take this
group retracement
I'll take it from the top of the
week
week to week I will join it
the normally Victor wig
will give you the good results
which I have seen personally
so let us close the test this
anchor points
yeah
and now
let us check what we draw this
White
okay
so if you see this you know it is
[Music]
on this
line that is one two one four so many
times it is taken a support and
resistance it's going on
so that means this was one point
where the stock was taking support
address so that means what we are doing
this temporary now the hip replacement
to identify further next upcoming
support and distance is okay fine so now
even if you see this
closely
at
1302 1302
it does touch so now if this crosses
then the flag pattern
know this
black pattern
this crosses it will move here
that is 1300 rupees
[Music]
and again if it causes thousand three
hundred it goes to 376.
see we have seen the support and
resistance with the line also but here
we are checking with Pip because some
people would like very accurately what
will be the support and resistance level
you know it needs for some internet
people
so that's the reason it is drawn here
to get exact grade at least I would say
98 percent
it will come great
because already we are seeing it
so even if you see in the weekly frame
yeah Librium is also transferring see
the golden ratios how it naturally it is
answering
okay so now let us check
Candlestick chat button
remove this now
this means the market is in the sideways
now presently we cannot
predict that
you know either should be after and out
and then only we can say that can stick
better
in a positive way but however
in this presently it is we can't
conclude here
delivery percentage this we already
checked
the maybe the accumulation is going on
with you know 73 40 60 69 and 50 percent
[Music]
some accommendations going on yes
so we analyze this talk so I would say
that
for a long term we analyze this from the
long term perspective
in long term it will give again
thousand seven hundred this is what it
says
thousand seven hundred will touch
so how many days it will touch in how
many days
this we can can know that but
let us try
date range
from here
[Music]
till here
321 days it has taken
240 bars I need to take the same amount
of days
you can say almost
[Music]
here
okay so overall
it's a good stock it's a Bluetooth stock
from insurance point of view yes we can
consider this
okay friends
thanks for watching and hope this
analysis was helpful
so see you in the next video
[Music]
to bring your topics